<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">BakaReader EX</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="light_novels">Light Novels</string>
    <string name="watch_list">Watch List</string>
    <string name="originals">Originals List</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_light_novels">Light Novels</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_light_novel_chapters">Light Novel Chapters</string>
    <string name="novel_title">title</string>
    <string name="novel_cover">cover</string>
    <string name="novel_synopsys"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_synopsys">Novel Synopsis</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_novel_content">Novel Content</string>
    <string name="invert_colors">Invert Colors</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_image">Image Viewer</string>
    <string name="novel_last_update">last update</string>
    <string name="novel_chapter">Novel Chapter</string>
    <string name="novel_chapter_dl">(DL)</string>
    <string name="list_empty">List is Empty</string>
    <string name="service_name">LNReader Update</string>
    <string name="hint_search">Search</string>
    <string name="teasers">Teaser List</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="novel_only">Novel Only</string>
    <string name="task_loading">Task still loading&#8230;</string>
    <string name="jump_last_read">Resume Novel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_bookmark">Bookmarksy</string>
    <string name="main_activity_menu">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_download_list">Downloads List</string>
    <string name="downloadsList">Downloads</string>
    <string name="title_activity_download_list_adapter">Downloads List</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_novel_pager">Light Novel Lists</string>
    <string name="title_activity_update_history">Update History</string>
    
    <string name="bakatsuki_copyrights">\nTLG Translation Common Agreement v.0.4.1
			\n0) \"Wiki\" is defined as the site \"Baka\-Tsuki\" running on any variation of wiki-like content management package, as defined by The American Heritage® Dictionary of the English Language, Fourth Edition. Houghton Mifflin Company, 2004.
			\na) \"Work\" is defined as any material from the product/service their respective copyright holders hold including, but not limited to, scripts(translated and original), dialogue, illustrations, screenshots, animation, clips, sound, etc. When the word \"translated\" is used before (a), (a) becomes \"translated and/or raw script\". b1) \"You\", \"your\" are defined as a copyright holder of the works as defined in (a) . b2) \"You\", \"your\" are defined as the submitter of the translated works as defined in (a) . b3) \"You\", \"your\" are defined as the viewer of the works as defined in (a) . b4) \"we\" is defined as the owner of this wiki AND the translators of the works as defined in (a) . c) \"I\", \"me\", \"my\" are defined as the owner of this wiki. d) \"licenced\" is defined as global and/or English publishing rights.
			\nBy entering this wiki(0) you agree to the following conditions. If you do not agree with this agreement, portion and/or full, please leave this wiki(0) now.
			\nSection A.1 All works(a), original and/or translated, belong to their respective copyright holders in their respective countries.
			\nThis wiki(0) is done with the intention to A) Improve my(c) English writing skills. B) To provide a storage space for fans of the translated works(a) so that the fans can promote these works(a) C) To attract more readers to make English licensing(d) possible.
			\nIf you(b1) feel your(b1) rights are being violated due to the usage of this wiki up to, but not limited by the presentation/broadcast/showing/distribution of works(a) in their original and/or translated full and/or portion of the work(a), please notify me(c) as soon as possible.
			\nAll works(a) will be deleted without warning upon request by their copyright holders.
			\n
			\nSection A.2 Under no circumstances would the visitors of this wiki(0), the translators of the works(a), the owner of this wiki(c,0), or the owner of this server assume any responsibilities for any damages that may have been caused by this wiki(0). Furthermore, by agreeing to this agreement, you(b1) agree to the notion that while I(c) did everything I(c) could to honor the copyrights of the work(a), accident can happen.
			\nSection B Under no circumstances would you(b2) 1. submit works(a) that are licenced(d) in the country the server and/or the submitter is located in. 2. submit translated works(a) copied directly from an unauthorized source such as, but not limited to, online, written sources etc. . If you(b2) submit works(a) that have been authorized by their rights holder, permission, in the form of written/electronic/printed must be available upon request. All translated works(a) rights are properties of their respective translators. By submitting translated works(a) to this wiki(0) you(b2) agree that All works(a) will be deleted without warning upon request by the copyright holders..
			\nSection C Under no circumstances would you(b3) 1. take full and/or portion of the (translated) works(a) in this wiki(0) and use them(a) to engage in any commercial activities such as, but not limited to, rent, sell, print, auction, broadcast etc. 2. claim translated works(a) in this wiki(0) as your(b3) own products of translation unless you(b3) are qualified as defined in (b2).
			\nSection D You(b3) agree with the notion that owner of this wiki(0), and all the submitters as defined in (b2), take no responsibility of any inappropriate material such as, but not limited to, pornography, violence, and offensive slurs. Furthermore, you(b3) agree with the notion that the owner of this wiki(0), and all the submitters as defined in (b2), by good wills try their best to moderate any material that may be suspected to be inappropriate in \"the owner of this wiki(0), and all the submitters as defined in (b2)\"\'s countries UNLESS such material is deemed necessary solely by the merit of preserving the integrity of such work(a). In this case, the consideration of integrity of such work(a) may take precedent before other considerations as mentioned previously in Section D.
			\n
			\nFinally, Have Fun! :D
			\nthelastguardian \- May 26, 2008</string>

</resources>